<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<odoo>
    <data noupdate="0">

        <record id="quality_communications_company" model="company.partners">
            <field name="name">Quality Communications Company</field>
            <field name="image" type="base64"
                   file="theme_cim/static/src/images/partners/quality_communications_company.png"/>
            <field name="description">(A national company established in 2009 AD by Resolution No. (441) for the year
                2009 AD, and Resolution No. (442) regarding its articles of association, and it is wholly owned by the
                Public Authority for Communications and Informatics. It was activated at the beginning of the second
                quarter of 2010
                The company is specialized in establishing, implementing, operating, maintaining and managing systems
                and centers for wired and wireless communication and information technology for emergencies and public
                safety dictated by the needs of the state and contracting for their implementation)
            </field>
            <field name="url">https://www.enc.ly</field>
        </record>

        <record id="libyan_international_telecom_company" model="company.partners">
            <field name="name">Libyan International Telecom Company</field>
            <field name="image" type="base64"
                   file="theme_cim/static/src/images/partners/libyan_international_telecom_company.png"/>
            <field name="description">It is one of the subsidiaries of the Libyan Post, Telecommunications and
                Information Technology Holding Company, and it was established in 2008 to take over Managing all
                international communication ports in Libya and meeting the international communication needs of the
                group of companies affiliated with the Libyan Post Company And communications and technology, whether
                telephone communications or data services, and the establishment of the Libyan International
                Telecommunication Company came out of faith Deep in the importance of international communication in the
                advancement and development of the educational and work environment in any society and in response to
                the increasing demand for services International communications and the Internet in Libya.
            </field>
            <field name="url">https://lptic.ly</field>
        </record>

        <record id="al_bunia_investment_and_services_company" model="company.partners">
            <field name="name">Al Bunnia Investment and Services Company</field>
            <field name="image" type="base64"
                   file="theme_cim/static/src/images/partners/al_bunia_investment_and_services_company.png"/>
            <field name="description">(Labiba Company is owned by the Libyan Holding Company for Communications and
                Information Technology, which is a company specialized in investment and services It has 7 branches and
                32 offices spread over all cities and regions of Libya And services, a large number of assets,
                represented by 950 service and investment properties and nearly 600 main and subsidiary communication
                towers spread over All parts of Libya, Al Bunia invests these assets in developing its resources and
                developing the infrastructure)
            </field>
            <field name="url">https://bounya.ly</field>
        </record>

        <record id="libyan_post_communications_and_information_technology_holding_company" model="company.partners">
            <field name="name">Libyan Post, Communications and Information Technology Holding Company</field>
            <field name="image" type="base64"
                   file="theme_cim/static/src/images/partners/libyan_post_communications_and_information_technology_holding_company.png"/>
            <field name="description">The holding company was established in accordance with the Cabinet Resolution No.
                63 of 2005 AD in order to be a holding company that owns telecommunications companies The big ones,
                namely, Libyana, Al-Madar, and Libya for Communications and Technology, the new generation of
                technology, international communications, and Libya's phone, as these are Companies have a major role in
                developing telephony, mobile phones, and Internet connectivity, and they have raised the efficiency of
                communications in Libya and enabling the largest possible number of citizens to obtain Internet service,
                whether through mobile phone companies Such as Libyana and Al-Madar or through the main Internet service
                provider such as the Libya Telecom and Technology Company LTT or a telephone company Libya, which
                provides wireless and wired phone service, as well as the Internet
                The holding company was established for the purpose of investing in the communications infrastructure in
                the country and abroad, and the company has a group of investments inside
                The country and abroad, some of them date back to the time of the General Post, Telecommunications and
                Telecommunications Company, which was dissolved in 2010
            </field>
            <field name="url">https://lptic.ly</field>
        </record>

        <record id="new_orbit_company" model="company.partners">
            <field name="name">New Orbit Company</field>
            <field name="image" type="base64"
                   file="theme_cim/static/src/images/partners/new_orbit_company.png"/>
            <field name="description">Al-Madar Al-Jadeed Company is one of the subsidiaries of the Libyan Holding
                Company for Communications and Information Technology, and it was established in 1996
                The company also began providing its services to the public in 1997, classifying Al-Madar Al-Jadid as
                the first mobile operator in the country
                Libya
            </field>
            <field name="url">https://www.almadar.ly</field>
        </record>

        <record id="libya_telecom_and_technology" model="company.partners">
            <field name="name">Libya Telecom and Technology</field>
            <field name="image" type="base64"
                   file="theme_cim/static/src/images/partners/libya_telecom_and_technology.png"/>
            <field name="description">A Libyan joint stock company established in 1997 and started its work as the first
                Internet service provider in Libya in early September 1999, and later it was annexed to the General Post
                and Telecommunications Company. Its service was initially limited to the Internet service via dial-up,
                then the dedicated line service, and with the years other services were added to it. For both
                individuals and business.
                She is the official registrar of the national domain name Ly for Libya and worked on establishing the
                Libyana mobile phone company in 2004, which later became independent as the largest mobile network in
                Libya.
            </field>
            <field name="url">https://www.ltt.ly</field>
        </record>

        <record id="libyana_mobile_phone" model="company.partners">
            <field name="name">Libyana mobile phone</field>
            <field name="image" type="base64"
                   file="theme_cim/static/src/images/partners/libyana_mobile_phone.png"/>
            <field name="description">Libyana began its work in Libya in September 2004, and during this short period,
                Libyana made great achievements.
                Wireless communications that support mobile phone services in various regions of Libya, and have
                continued to upgrade services by providing Internet and messaging services
                Multimedia and voice mail across its network, and it was the pioneer in providing third generation
                telephone line service at the northern level
                Africa in September 2006, and the company aspires to spread and reach every home and city. It has
                established no less than 15 service centers in
                Various regions, reaching more than 6,200,000 subscribers during its years of operation, or 116% of the
                population
            </field>
            <field name="url">https://www.libyana.ly/Default.aspx</field>
        </record>

        <record id="new_generation_technology_company" model="company.partners">
            <field name="name">New Generation Technology Company</field>
            <field name="image" type="base64"
                   file="theme_cim/static/src/images/partners/new_generation_technology_company.png"/>
            <field name="description">The establishment of the New Generation Technology Company came to contribute to
                improving and developing the local telecommunications market by transferring and localizing technologies
                Modern telecommunications in a way that enables the company to compete locally and internationally, by
                providing all services
                Integrated communications from fixed and mobile phone services, the Internet, video broadcast services,
                and next generation network services
                The new generation of technology is the first integrated operator in Libya, which is pursuing a strategy
                based on diversity and integration in providing services
                Its goal is to win customer satisfaction
            </field>
            <field name="url">https://aljeel.ly</field>
        </record>

        <record id="libya_post_company" model="company.partners">
            <field name="name">Libya Post Company</field>
            <field name="image" type="base64"
                   file="theme_cim/static/src/images/partners/libya_post_company.png"/>
            <field name="description">It is a Libyan joint stock company with a legal personality and an independent
                financial disclosure, and it is affiliated with the Libyan Post and Telecommunications Company
                Information Technology Holding
                It aims to establish, operate, manage and regulate all types of different postal services, including
                postal financial services, at the domestic level
                External marketing of services and products for the benefit of public and private entities, and any
                complementary activity aimed at achieving their objectives
            </field>
            <field name="url">https://libyapost.ly</field>
        </record>

        <record id="libya_telephone_company" model="company.partners">
            <field name="name">Libya Telephone Company</field>
            <field name="image" type="base64"
                   file="theme_cim/static/src/images/partners/libya_telephone_company.png"/>
            <field name="description">Libya Phone Company is the cornerstone of the telecommunications world in Libya,
                as the company was established by a decision of the management committee
                The Libyan Post, Communications and Information Technology Company (Holding) No. (4) 2008
                For the purposes of operating, maintaining and developing a national telephone network, which includes
                the local systems represented by transit switches, sub-divisions, and media
                Connecting within cities and providing all services to secure service for individual subscribers and
                legal entities, and providing any complementary activity for the purpose of achieving their objectives.
                Provided that the company seeks to contribute to building and developing the society's economy through
                the actions it provides and maintaining the values, principles and ideals
                the society
            </field>
            <field name="url">https://hlc.ly</field>
        </record>

    </data>
</odoo>